UNITE Legislative Department Records 6000/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Legislative Department Records
1938-2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/007
51.11 cubic feet
51.1 linear ft.
Records.
5748435
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 19, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/007 AV: UNITE Legislative Department Audio-Visual Materials
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union -- Archives.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees -- Archives.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Legislative Department.; UNITE HERE (Organization) -- Archives
5748435
- White House Group - Hours of Work Proposals, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Outreach, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Membership Subcommittee, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Sweatshops: White House Group 1/23/96 Meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission Minutes 9/4/96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission 9/30/96 Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission 9/30/96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission 9/30 Meeting Handouts, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission 10/11, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Sweatshop - White House Group 11/1/96, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- White House Group - 11/18/96 Conference Call, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission 12/6/96 Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Sweatshops: White House Group 1/8/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- White House Group: Language Changes, Feb. 97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 2/3/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Sweatshops: White House Group 2/21/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Sweatshop: White House Group April 7, 1997 Meeting (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Final Report to White House, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Sweatshop: White House Group White House Meeting 4/14/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 5/9/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 6/17/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- White House Group: National Consumers League, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Sweatshops: White House Group Final Agreement Press, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Sweatshop: White House Group July 30, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 8/5/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Monitoring Conf. Call 9/22/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 9/26/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 10/14/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Alan's Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Brussels Conference, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Sweatshops: White House Group CEP Program, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Sweatshop: White House Group China, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Consumer Education, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Sweatshops: White House Group Final Agreement, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 11/24/97 Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission Monitoring, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Jan. 9, 1998 Meeting (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Post 1/9/98 Meeting (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 1/26/98, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 2/3/98 Meeting & Follow-up, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Sweatshop: white House group 3/6/98 Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 3/26/98 Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Sweatshop: White House Group 4/21/98 Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Sweatshop: White House Group After April 21, 1998 Meeting (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Sweatshops: White House Group July 98 Issues, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Antitrust Issue, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Joint Employer Issue, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Life Insurance Industry Standards, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Sweatshop: White House Living Wage, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Sweatshops: White House Group Participants, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Sweatshops: White House Group New Participants, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Membership Models, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Nike Frontlash Flap, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Sweatshop: White House Group Reaction to Report to White House, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Sweatshop: White House Group NCL Problem, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- White House Group: Summer 1998 Developments (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Sweatshop: Levy, Stan, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- White House Group Standards, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Sweatshops: White House Group Standards Pharis Document, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Sweatshops: White House Group Final Agreement Aftermath, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Sweatshops: White House Commission - Unite Materials, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- White House Group Press, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- White House Group: Governance, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Affirmative Action Background, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Background, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- American Jobs + Manufacturing Pres. Act 1355, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Background: Apparel Industry, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Background: Americans with Disabilities Act of 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Health Care - ILGWU Materials - 103rd Congress, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- ILGWU - Early Retiree Thing, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Health Care - Drugs, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Health Care Blue book, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Background - Beijing Conference, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Background: 1993 CBO Study (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Background: Child Labor Working teens in U.S., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Child Labor: Model State Law Background, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Balanced Budget 103rd Congress, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Balanced Budget Amendment - 104th Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Civil Rights - 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Civil Rights 1992 - Wards Cove (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Civil Rights Act of 1991 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Bankruptcy Reform 1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Harkin/Brown International Child Labor Bill, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Child Labor - Paper baler, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Child Labor - 104th Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- 104th Congress - Fact Sheets, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 40 Hour Week - House Bill - H.R. 2391, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Alternative, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- 160 Hour Bills, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 104th Congress - Comp. Time - Testimony, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- 104th Congress - Comp. Time - Exchange w/ L.P.A., 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- 104th Congress - Comp. Time - Polling, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Forty Hour Week: Clinton's Proposal, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Comp Time (105th Congress): AFL-CIO position, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Comp. Time: Clinton's Proposal 1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Comp Time - Unite Letters, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Comp. Time (105th Congress): HR 1, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Comp. Time (105th Congress) Fact Sheets, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Comp. Time: 54 - Ashcroft, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Comp. Time: HR 1 - Ballenger, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Comp. Time Vote - HR 1, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Family and Medical Leave: 104th Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Family and Medical Leave Act: 102nd Congress, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Family & Medical Leave: Data and Fact Sheets, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Family and Medical Leave - 103rd Congress, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- ILGWU Contract: Family & Medical Leave, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Family and Medical Leave Act - Company Policies + Programs, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Family Medical Leave Act - Vote, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- family and Medical Leave, HR 925, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Health Care, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- FTC Cases, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Health Care - Testimony 10/91, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- AAMA, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Abortion Issues - Choice, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Abortion Issue - Gag Rules, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Abortion Issue - UNITE position, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- The Accountability Project, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- ACTPN Designation, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Advanced Glassfiber Yarns, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Administration People, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Affirmative Action, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Africa Advocates, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- African Americans in a Recession, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Africa, National Summit, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Africa Summit, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Alfred Angelo, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- American Legislative Exchange Council, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- American Federation of Musicians, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- American Federation of Teachers, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- American Flags, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- American Samoa, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- American Textile Manufacturers Institute, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Apparel Job Loss, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Apparel Industry NY, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Auto Parts, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Bangladesh Workers Visit, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Bangladesh, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Baucus, Sen. - Max, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Beyer Mfg. co., 1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Black Berets, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Black Uniform & Cap Co., 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Budget Resolution H.R. 83, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Budget - 1981: Explanation of Budget Process Reconciliation Rules (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Budget Appropriation, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Budget Resolution FY: 2003, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- B.L.S., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Bush, George, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Bush Cabinet Appointments, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Beck, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Candidate Questionnaires, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Campaign Reform 2001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Campaign Finance Reform, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Campaign Finance Civil rights Issue, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Campaign Reform, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Campaign Reform: HR 3465 UNITE Materials, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Campaign Finance Reform - Money, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Carter Industries, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Cash Balance Pension Plans, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- CEDAW, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Chemical Safety of Health Investigation Board, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Chentex, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Child Care, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Child Care - 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Child Labor: AFL-CIO Materials, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Child Labor: Background Info., 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- HR 434 Enforcement, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Child Labor: Domestic, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Child Labor: DOL 1996 Report (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Child Labor: 1996 Child Labor Conference (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Child Labor Coalition: 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Child Labor: 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Child Labor: D.O.C. Reports 1993, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Child Labor: DOL Report 2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Child Labor: Driving, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Child Labor: Free the Children, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Child Labor: Harkin Bills: S.332, S.554, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Child Labor: ILAB Hearing Testimony, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Child Labor: Iqbal Masih, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Child Labor: ILO New Convention, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Child Labor: India, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Child Labor: JCPA Speech, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Child Labor: Link to Trade, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Child Labor Coalition: Resource Sheets, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Child Labor Rugmark Campaign, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Sweatshop Coalitions, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- HR 2475 Bonded Child Labor, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Child Labor Sanders Amendment, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Child Labor - Soccerballs, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Child Labor: Unicef Report, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Civil Rights Technology, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Child Labor Working Groupmeeting, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Children in the Fields, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Child Prostitution & Pornography, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Clean Money, Clean Elections, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Clerical Offshore Work, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- CLUW: Sexual Harassment Project, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Clothes for a Change, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Coalition for Justice in the Maquiladoras, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Coalition to Stop Gun Violence, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Coca-Cola Discrimination Class Action, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Consumer Choice & Corp. Responsibility 4/29/96 Hearing, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Cmte. On Educ., Labor and Workforce Dev. May 10-12, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Consumer Issues, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Contingent Workers, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Contraception, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Contractor Responsibility Rule, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Corporate Welfare, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- AFL Meeting Notes, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- CTC Flap, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Cuba, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Dayton Hudson Care, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Debt Relief, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Department of Labor, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- DOL - Leadership, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- DOL Pamphlets, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Department of Labor: Dislocated Workers, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- DOL Report on Wages Etc. In Apparel Producing Countries, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Peter Deutsch (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Digital Empowerment Steering Cmte., 2001 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Domestic Linen, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Domestic Violence, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Duro Workers, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Dry Cleaning, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Dry Cleaning Environmental Tax Credit of 1999 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- E-Commerce Task Force, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Economic Report of the President 2001 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Earned Income Tax Credit, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Economics Education, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Economy, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Electric Deregulation, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Electronic Ford Transfer, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- El Paso: Job Training Program, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Education, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Edwards, Sen. John, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- EEO Executive Order, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- EEOC Best Practices, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- EEOC + Media Diversity, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Energy: Conference Report, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- English Only, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Employment Discrimination Against Midlife and Older Women, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Emp. Retirement Income Security Act 1997 Report to Congress (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Emport-Import Bank 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Fair Trade Organizers Conference, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Fair Pay Act 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Fair Act HR 1987 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Fair Pay Act - 107th Congress, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- FLSA - 2001 Minimum Wage (Box 8, Folder 9)
- FLSA - Public Sector Coverage, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- FLSA Pay Docking, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Salary Basis Test, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- FLSA & Incentive Systems HR 3087, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Fair Labor Standards Act Good Faith Defense, 1984-1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Amendments to Fair Labor Standards Act, 1938-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Family Medical Leave Act New Jersey, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Family & Medical Leave Act SEIU Guide, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Family & Medical Leave Act Paid, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Families USA, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Family Income to Respond to Significant Transitions Insurance Act H.R. 226, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Family Leave Income Campaign Advisory, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Family Leave: Lynn Woolsey Project, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Federal Election Commission, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Fiber Industry, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Fingerhut Liquidation, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- First Contract Stats, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Flammability, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Freshmen Visits 2001 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Garden State Tanning, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Unite Major Market Negotiations 1997 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Unite - Garment Industry Contracts, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Gatt & Natl. Retirement Fund, 1994-2000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Health Care: AFL Policy Group, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Fruit of Loom, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Health Care: 2001 Developments (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Health Care: Health Coverage 2000 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Health Care: Kennedy Kassebaum Regs., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Health Care: PBOR (4/14/2000) (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Health Care: Medicare RX, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Health Care: Real Reform, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Health Care Task Force, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Health Care: Tax Credits, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Health Care: Quality Standard, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Hispanic Demographic, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Hollander Strike, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Homeland Security, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- ILAB Appropriations Language, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Election 96 Analysts, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- ILO, 1960-1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- ILO New Convention: Abolishing Extreme Forms of Child Labour, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- ILO Report on Globalization of TCF Industries, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Immigration: 1997 Law Changes (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Immigration: 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Immigration 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Immigration 1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Immigration: AFL-CIO Brochures (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Immigration: AFL-CIO Policy, 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Immigration: AFL-CIO Group 1999, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Immigration: AFL Policy Shift 2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Immigration: Anti-Discrimination Provision, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Immigration: Benefits, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Immigration: Connecticut, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Immigration: Conyers Bill 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Immigration: Commission Report, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Immigration: Detention, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Immigration Farmworkers Hza Visas, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Immigration Food Stamps, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Immigration: General Stuff, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Immigration: Guestworker, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Immigration: Freshmen Visits 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Immigration HR 2202 Final, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Immigration: HR2202 Unite Analysis, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Immigration: INS/DOL Mou, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Immigration: Immigrant Fairness Restoration Act of 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Immigration: INS Restructuring, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Immigration: Labor Certs, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Immigration Labor Laws Immigration Status, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Immigration: Legal Issues 1999 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Immigration: 105th Congress Legal Immigration, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Immigration: Legal Immigration, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Immigration: Low Wage Immigrant Worker: 106th Congress, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Immigration: Motor Voter, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Immigration: Voter ID Check HR1428, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Immigration: Industrialization Backlog, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Immigration: NLRB Backpay, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Immigration: NLRB Cases, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Immigration: Opposition, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Immigration: Phone and Fax Numbers, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Immigration: Refugees (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Immigration - Social Security, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Immigration - State Laws, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Immigration Task Force, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Immigration: Trafficking, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Immigration: Union Group, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Immigration: Unite Fact Sheets, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Immigration: Unite Views, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Immigration: Western Hemisphere Group (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Immigration and Naturalization Workplace Issues, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Immigration - Workplace Executive Order, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Immigration: Workplace Issues, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Latino and Immigrant Fairness Act S. 2912, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Independent Contractor Clarification Act HR. 1525, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- International Right to Know, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Invest in America, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Invision, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- IPS, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- ITG Newsletters, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Jamaica, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Jays Dinner, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Jobber Liability Suit Lopez V. Silverman, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Justice Anti - Slavery Task Force, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Kate Mullany House, Troy, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Kimi in Honduras, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Koret of California, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Kudjo Sogadzi, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Labels: Best Known, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Labor Advisory Committee on Trade, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Labor Law: State Public Sector, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Labor History, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Labor Movement, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Laundry Contracts, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Legislative Priorities 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Mark Levinson, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Limbaugh. Rush Neckties, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Limited English Proficiency, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Lion Apparel, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Living Wage Campaign: College Logo Campaign, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Living Wage Campaigns, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Lobbying, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Unite Lobby Day: April 12, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- March 21 Lobby Day, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Low Wage Workers, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Made in USA Organizational, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Marty Granoff, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Manufacturing Policy, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Maurituis, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Medicare, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Medicare 106th, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Medicare Dual Eligibiles, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Medicare RX - State Bills, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Men's & Boy's Wear Directory 1997 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Men's Wear Industry, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- April 3 + 4, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Senate Minimum Wage (S.25381), 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Minimum Wage (2001), 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Minimum Wage, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Minimum Wage: Impact on Unite Contracts, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Minimum Wage: Facts, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Minimum Wage 1999: S192; HR325 (Box 10, Folder 49)